PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: **DO TRUNG DUC**Designation: Full Stack Developer

• DOB: 01/02/1998

Mail: Duc010298@gmail.comPhone: (+84) 962 481 497 (VN)

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

 2023-Now Master of software engineering (MSE), FPT School of Business and Technology (FSB)

• 2016-2020 Bachelor Degree of Software Engineering, FPT University

CERTIFICATES

N/A

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

 Highly motivated and versatile Fullstack Developer with over 4+ years of experience leading and building complex web applications for various industries, including manufacturing and healthcare. Proven ability to work effectively in both backend and frontend development, utilizing a wide range of programming languages and frameworks (Python Django, Java Spring, Angular, VueJS, etc.) and deploy systems on cloud platforms (AWS). Possesses strong leadership skills with experience managing and mentoring development teams. Demonstrated success in delivering critical projects on time and within budget.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

| Skill | Proficiency | Experience | |
|-----------------------|--------------|------------|--|
| Programming Languages | | | |
| Python | Advanced | 4y | |
| Java | Advanced | 4y | |
| Javascript/Typescript | Advanced | 4y | |
| C# | Intermediate | 1y | |
| Web Apps Development | | | |
| Django | Advanced | 4y | |
| Flask | Intermediate | 1y | |
| Spring Framework | Advanced | 4y | |
| ExpressJS | Advanced | 2y | |

| ASP.Net | Intermediate | 1y |
|-----------------|--------------------|----|
| Angular | Advanced | 4y |
| VueJS | Intermediate | 2y |
| OS/Cloud | | |
| Windows | Advanced | 4y |
| CentOS | Advanced | 4y |
| Ubuntu | Advanced | 4y |
| AWS Cloud | Intermediate | 1y |
| DB/Queues/Cache | | |
| PostgreSQL | Advanced | 4y |
| MariaDB | Intermediate | 1y |
| RabbitMQ | Intermediate | 2y |
| Kafka | Intermediate | 1y |
| Redis | Limited Experience | 6m |
| CI/CD, Tools | | |
| Jenkins | Limited Experience | 1y |
| Gitlab-CI | Intermediate | 3y |
| Docker | Advanced | 4y |
| Gitlab | Advanced | 4y |

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English IntermediateJapanese Conversational

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

| Duration | 01/2024 - 03/2024 | |
|----------------|---|--|
| Team Size | 34 | |
| Position | Backend Developer | |
| Description | Built a Warehouse Control System (WCS) for a big Japanese company. | |
| Responsibility | Designed and implemented APIs to improve system efficiency. | |
| | Resolved critical project issues and ensured timely project delivery. | |
| | Built and deployed source code on AWS Cloud servers. | |
| Technology | Python Django, Postgres, AWS Cloud | |

| Duration | 10/2023 – 02/2024 |
|-------------|---|
| Team Size | 8 |
| Position | Fullstack Developer (Technical leader) |
| Description | A system that modifies the avatar authentication function using NFT, AI |
| | Model Warmark, and interacts with other systems via API. |

| Responsibility | Analyze and fix system bugs based on client requests. Analyze requirements, develop and implement new features (front-end and back-end). Deploy the system on AWS Cloud. Resolve critical project issues and provide technical support to team members. |
|----------------|--|
| Technology | Java Spring, Angular, Python Flask, MariaDB, Microservices |

| Duration | 03/2023 – 10/2023 |
|----------------|--|
| Team Size | 94 |
| Position | Fullstack Developer (Technical leader) |
| Description | A big Japanese company need to build a web app system to improve work |
| | efficiency and digitize information at the manufacturing site, including the |
| | following applications: |
| | 1. Face Recognition Module |
| | 2. Education Management Application |
| | 3. Deployment Management Application |
| Responsibility | Define the architecture, setup the environments for the Face Recognition |
| | Module. |
| | Designed and developed APIs for the Face Recognition Module, including |
| | functions such as face recognize authentication using SDK, employee |
| | entry and exit management in the factory, authentication history |
| | management, and data synchronization between offline client and server. |
| | Develop the user interface (frontend) for the Face Recognition Module. |
| | Resolve critical project issues and provide technical support to team |
| | members. |
| Technology | Python Django, Angular, PostgreSQL, ElectronJS |

| Duration | 05/2021 - 04/2023 | |
|----------------|---|--|
| Team Size | 62 | |
| Position | Fullstack Developer (Team Leader) | |
| Description | Developed a digital transformation (DX) solution for the manufacturing industry | |
| | of a big Japanese company, providing various applications for different areas | |
| | within manufacturing, including: | |
| | Production Management | |
| | Quality Management | |
| | Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul (MRO) | |
| | Supply Chain Management | |
| | Data Analysis | |
| Responsibility | Analyzed customer requirements based on basic design and created | |
| | detailed design. | |

| | Implemented the solution (for both back-end and front-end) for key . |
|------------|--|
| | systems. |
| | Deployed the system to servers and managed servers. |
| | Assigned and managed the work of team members. |
| | Provided technical support for team members. |
| Technology | Java Spring, Python Django, Python Flask, Angular, VueJS, PostgreSQL |

| Duration | 03/2020 – 5/2021 | |
|----------------|--|--|
| Team Size | 8 | |
| Position | Fullstack Developer (Technical leader) | |
| Description | Clinic Management System | |
| | Developed a web application for managing a multidisciplinary clinic, including functionalities for patient reception, clinical and paraclinical examinations, result management and printing, medical history management, inventory management, and payment. | |
| Responsibility | Communicate with customers and teammates to gather and clarify requirements. Design system architecture and deploy the system on internal servers. Design database schema. Design UX/UI and implement solutions (both back-end and front-end) based on user requirements. Troubleshoot complex project issues and provide technical support to team members. | |
| Technology | Python Django, Angular, PostgreSQL | |

| Duration | 08/2019 – 01/2020 |
|----------------|---|
| Team Size | 70 |
| Position | Junior Developer |
| Description | Develop an application for comprehensive management of employee activities in |
| | the factory of a big Japanese company. |
| | The client wants to use this application to collect, store, display and |
| | analyze data throughout via the internal web. |
| Responsibility | Develop and fix bugs for the application based on requirements. |
| | Develop small modules of the system. |
| | Write system documentation. |
| Technology | Java Spring, Angular, PostgreSQL, Microservices |